So now that we have the dream solution, and
现在我们有了理想方案
we all decide it's best, we move to prototyping, right?
而且是共同决定的最优决策 下面可以进入原型设计了 是吗？
>> That's right.
是的
Prototyping is a wonderful way to test your ideas.
原型设计是验证创意的绝佳途径
In fact, we want to make prototypes that are real enough to feel, so
实际上 我们要制成足够真实的原型
that we can test them with users, and that's all that's required.
以进行用户测试 这就是我们需要做的
Prototyping can take many forms.
原型设计可采用多种形式
The simplest is to do a paper prototype where you can quickly gather feedback.
最简单的莫过于纸面原型 你可以快速收集反馈
One level up from that is to work on digital designs that are mid fidelity or
再高级一点的是中、高保真
high fidelity.
数字模型设计
The higher the fidelity the easier it is to test and to get feedback from users
保真度越高越容易测试并获得用户反馈
because they're looking something that's a little bit more polished.
因为用户看到的模型更精致
A next level of prototyping is actually creating physical prototypes.
再高一个层次的原型设计是创建实体原型
When we work on something like Project Glass at Google or Project Moon, it's
设计 Google Project Glass 或 Project Loon 这类产品时
not about software always, it's about what does the physical device look like?
关键点不在软件 而在于如何呈现实体装置
So that's when it's useful to have materials that
所以 拥有能让你快速塑造总体创意的材料
help you create a quick shape of a general idea.
会对你有所助益
Other prioritizes we have made include video.
其他首选形式还包括视频
In fact, if you try to explain the product to some one,
实际上 如果你想向他人介绍产品
creating a video is super, super useful.
制作一个视频会非常、非常有用
>> Yeah, Dropbox did that.
Dropbox 就这么做的
>> That's right.
是的
>> [LAUGH] The little how to videos that a lot of companies use to
在设计阶段 小小的说明视频真得很有用
describe their services are really useful in the design phase.
许多公司都用来展示其服务项目
If you make it straight on, even if it's shot with a little mobile phone,
如果想更直观 用手机拍摄短片也可以
and the users are the friends that you're working with.
而用户则是你的工作伙伴
That can be sufficient to explain the idea to a user, or to an investor, and
这样就足以向用户或投资者说明创意
to test it.
并进行测试了
If you want the high quality prototype, you need to spend longer developing it.
如果你想得到高质量原型 就需要更长的开发时间
>> So I can actually code it.
我可以编代码来实现
>> That's right.
是的
I think coding a prototype is a great idea, so some people are able
我觉得代码构建原型的主意不错
to really sprint, and within two days, start to already call the prototype.
一些人真正冲刺起来 不到两天就能做出像样的原型
And then you can have an interactive demo.
之后就有了互动样本
Or some people take maybe four or five days,
一些人或许要花上四五天制作原型
depending on how complex the solution is.
这取决于解决方案的复杂程度
So the duration of the prototyping
原型设计阶段的时间
phase is usually what determines the duration of the sprint.
通常会决定冲刺的时间
This is the key aspect in which actually the work is getting made.
这是达成任务的关键方面
If you're someone who loves to code, who loves to design,
如果你喜爱编程 喜爱设计
this is the phase that you really get to shine.
在这个阶段你就可以大显身手了
And if you're looking for a low fidelity prototype, a short sprint,
若你寻求的是低保真原型、短时冲刺
a few hours might be sufficient.
几个小时或许就够了
If you want something that's high fidelity, or requires a demo or
若想要高保真原型或需要样本或视频
a video, you're better advised to have a whole week of the team's time so
建议最好给团队一周的时间
you can make something beautiful.
这样才能慢工出细活
>> How do I know which to choose, if I choose a high fidelity or low fidelity?
我怎么知道是该用高保真还是低保真原型？
What is the best?
哪个更好？
>> Okay, so, if you're working on a new product, it's probably best to shoot for
你如果正在开发一款新产品 可能最佳选择会是
medium fidelity.
中保真原型
That means that you're not looking at paper prototypes necessarily.
这样你就不必盯着纸面原型
You might have some early wire frames,
你可以有一些早期线框图
and that you're starting to put some color on them.
并着手给图上色
Or that you also use Keynote or a quick prototyping tool that
或者也可以使用 Keynote 或快速原型设计工具
your engineers know how to use in order to bring some life to the ideas.
你的工程师都会用 让创意鲜活起来
We believe in teams choosing their own prototyping tools.
相信团队会选用自己的原型设计工具
There's a lot that's available on the market, and
很多在市面上有售
the right ones are the ones your team loves to use.
团队爱用的工具才是对的选择
If you're wondering where to start, Sketch is a really great example.
如果你想知道从何入手  Sketch 就非常不错
So is Adobe Suite, although it does take a little bit of time to learn.
Adobe Suite 也不错 虽然学习它要花点时间
And then Keynote and
还有 Keynote 和 Google Sites
Google Sites are also really useful in prototyping quickly.
对快速原型设计也颇有帮助